MUNSEONG JEONG

Mobile: 0452462858 Email: jmunseng@gmail.com

Carlton, VIC 3053

Portfolio: https://www.leonjeong.com/

I have many years of front-end and design working experience and familiar with HTML, CSS, JavaScript also experienced using numerous programming languages/tools including React, Typescript, NodeJs, MySQL, Git. During the university I also used Java, PHP, C++, C#, Python languages on assignment projects. I enjoy learning new languages and development techniques. Based on designer experience I am good to use of PS, Ai, Figma and AdobeXD tools. I am also adapt quickly to different working environments and I am a good team player that received many positive feedback from colleagues.

EXPERIENCE

FrontEnd Developer (volunteer project)

May 2022- Present

Trans Tasman Energy Group

Melbourne, Victoria, Australia

TTEG is providing solutions of energy requirements for the large, small and medium businesses.

Developing a customer management system.

My responsibilities were:

- Created Retailer, Company, Council and Association list and detail pages.
- Fetch the data from API then filter or sort them.
- Technologies used: React, Typescript, Material UI, Git, Bitbucket,
- Agile mode develop environment
- Deploy the website to the server.
- Design the layout of the website.
- Communicated with customers to discuss their needs.

Analyst Programmer

Oct 2019 - Mar 2022

EASI Australia pty Itd

Melbourne, Victoria, Australia

EASI Australia is running the most popular asian food delivery platform in Australia.

My responsibilities were:

- Creating and maintaining websites, including desktop and mobile user interface pages and admin system pages, mainly based on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, W2UI, JSP and Java.
- Test, debug and fix errors of Web accessibility (HTML, CSS).
- Test, debug, diagnose and correct errors in users' strategic reporting and analytical functions.
- Develop and design strategic reporting and analytical functions to meet business requirements (SQL, Tableau).
- Provide advice in developing strategic reporting and analytical functions.
- Use Tableau to analyze data, generate visualization data, and allocate human resources according to the data.
- Take data from databases, mainly based on MySQL.
- Integrate data from various back-end services, systems, and databases.
- Maintaining UI design of the admin system and mobile app, mainly creating ad banners, posters and renewing layout of the app. Amend diversity food pictures, restaurant photos and menu (Photoshop).

Front-End Web Designer

May 2015 - Sep 2017

DamingGlass

Pocheon, Gyeonggi-do, Korea

DamingGlass is a global trading company. The core business is the purchase, shipping, and sale of original glass sheets from China to Korea. My responsibilities were:

- Established online stores from scratch based on WordPress and Cafe24 to enable customers to order products and track orders online, mainly using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, PHP.
- Design and amending product detail pages, model pictures, banners, thumbnails, ad posters.
- Managing product information on different e-commerce platforms, such as NaverShopping, Gmarket and 11 street stores.
- Management marketing based google ads and naver ads, and nested ads in above e-stores.
- Translating documents and contracts between Chinese and Korean.

Web Designer Jul 2013 - Apr 2015

Sappira

Uijeongbu, Gyeonggi-do, Korea

Sappira is a company that designs, produces, and sells clothing for medical and entertainment companies in Korea. My responsibilities were:

- Maintained product content across different online store platforms,
- Design and amending product detail pages, model pictures, banners, thumbnails, ad posters.
- Creating and maintaining user pages, mainly using HTML, CSS, JavaScript.
- Promote products through Korean actors, Instagram bloggers and facebook ads.

SKILLS

Programming Languages/Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, JQuery, Bootstrap, C, C#,

Python, Java, Material UI

Databases: MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB

Source Control: Git, GitHub

Communication Skills: communicate effectively in English, Mandarin and Korean.

EDUCATION

React Development May 2022 - Aug 2022

General Assambly

Majors: Frontend Development

Graduate Certificate of Business Analytics

Kaplan BUSINESS SCHOOL Dockland

Majors: Business Analytics

Bachelor of Information Technology

Mar 2018 - Nov 2020

Jul 2021 - Feb 2022

Deakin University, Burwood Majors: Application Development